A Guide to the Albert M. Brown Collection, 1930-1938
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Albert M. Brown Collection 1930-1938
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms2009-122
1 Box; 0.2 cu. ft.
Albert Brown graduated from Virginia Tech in 1938 with a degree in Agricultural Engineering. Collection consists of Virginia Tech memorabilia and class assignments from Brown's time at Virginia Tech. Materials date from 1930 through 1938.
Albert M. Brown
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
The Albert M. Brown Collection was donated to the University Archives in Special Collections in 2001.
Biographical Information
Albert Magruder Brown graduated from the Virginia Polytechnic Institute in 1938 with a degree in Agricultural Engineering. While attending VPI, Brown served in various capacities for the Virginia Agricultural Engineer. Brown was also involved with the American Society of Agricultural Engineers as well as the Mid-Tidewater Club and the 4-H Alumni Club. Brown was a member of the cheerleading squad his last three years and served as head cheerleader as a senior.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of Virginia Tech memorabilia and class assignments of Albert Brown dating from 1930 through 1938.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Virginia Polytechnic Institute Publications, 1930-1935 (Box-folder 1:1)
- Photographs - Individuals, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 1:2)
- Photographs - VPI Organizations and Athletic Teams, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 1:3)
- Events, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 1:4)
- Coursework and Assignments, 1936 (Box-folder 1:5)
- Bugle Supplement 1936 (Box-folder 1:6)
- 4-H Alumni Club, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 1:7)
- Papers on Power and Fuel Consumption, 1938 (Box-folder 1:8)
- Correspondence, 1938 (Box-folder 1:9)
- The Farm Outlook, 1938 (Box-folder 1:10)